So they added again, I'm headed out on this mission driven book tour and look, they're
trying to sabotage my book talks and signings by reserving all tickets available.
So even when I am showing up for free, they are trying to impede my ability to reach you.
These folks want to shut me up so crazy.
And you wonder like if what you're doing is right, then why you got a problem with folks?
So for anybody who wants to come to my book signings, of course, attempt to sign up because
the link is provided for you.
However, you can just show up.
I said it before and I'm going to say it again.
This ain't even really a book tour.
This is a mission.
It is a tool to continue to elevate our minds and our vibrations.
And I welcome you all to come join me.
So all my people in San Diego, Seattle, Chicago, Detroit, and the cities that I'm going to be
coming to in addition, we'll see you there with a fist in the air because we're going
to stand on truth.
We're going to stand on love and we're going to stand on business because that's what our
ancestors would want us to do.
Sister Seals, this is your ancestor.
See you there.
Head to AmandaSeals.com and get your tickets to the live stream performance and release
of my new book, What Would the Ancestors Say, on November 8th.
Also check out When I'll Be in Your City with my book tour.
See you then.
Pop, pop.
We'll be right back.